evok.in 2016-06-30

# Privacy Policy Evok.in

#### PRIVACY POLICY:

Evok.in appreciates your trust placed in us and ensures the privacy protection of all it’s users. Kindly read our privacy policy in detail before completing your online shopping with us.

This privacy policy explains how evok.in collects personal and non personal information (mandatory/ voluntary) and uses/discloses and protects such information through the website.

Personal information denotes the data that is used to uniquely identify or contact a single person. Personal information for the purpose of this policy shall include, but not limit to, information regarding user’s name, address, telephone no., date of birth, gender, email address etc. User needs to provide his/her personal information while using some services of evok.in. For an example while creating user ID/registering on the website, user provides information, while making an online purchase, user provides financial information.

Note: Our privacy policy is subject to change regularly/periodically, without notice. To ensure the updates on changes, kindly review the privacy policy periodically. This privacy policy doesn’t apply to any of our business partners/franchisee/associates or other third parties. Kindly review the privacy policy of other parties with whom you may interact.

We collect only such personal information that we believe to be relevant and is required to understand customers, their interests and their buying behavior, their preferences to provide them a customized website experience/to notify them on updates, new activities, latest contents available on the website, special offers, schemes, other products/services offered by evok.in, customer service or technical support issues etc.

By using our website, you agree to the terms and condition of this policy. If you do not agree with the terms and conditions of this policy, please do not proceed further to use this website.

We want you to feel comfortable using our website from your computer system/mobile sites and mobile applications. Kindly feel secure submitting your information to us and contact us in case of any question or concern regarding privacy on the site. Following are the FAQs regarding privacy policy that may occur in your mind. Kindly read the document carefully:

  * **What customer information does evok.in collect while online purchase of your furniture?**

We take customer’s contact details, e.g. your first and last name, billing and shipping address, mobile phone no or contact no., primary and alternate email address, Postal code, evok.in account password. While using credit card payment mode we ask your banking details e.g credit card number, cardholder’s name, card expiry date and CVV. Our payment gateway partner (Pay U) has ensured the highest safety standards and security of your information while transacting on evok.in.

We keep data of your previous transactions and orders including product, price, date of purchase, payment and transaction history etc.

Information related to optional online surveys on our or third party sites, posted by us. This information will include demographic profile (gender, age, income etc.) of responder and their preferred products and services, opinions of features on our websites, other information as per our registration process.

Cookies (A cookie is a small amount of data that is sent to a user's browser from a web server and is eventually stored on a user's computer hard drive.), your session logged information on our site, about the pages you visit/access i.e. your navigation within the site, the links you click on our site, number of times you access the page, number of times you have shopped on our website/mobile site/mobile applications, source of traffic, IP address, browser type/language, operating system, date and time of request etc. third party sign in information shared on our website, such as facebook, twitter, pinterest, sign in information, your information stored in archive on our servers even after the deletion or the termination of your account.

Email communication by you to evok.in regarding product assistance, store inquiry, sales order or post sales service related communication etc.

  * **What customer information does evok.in consider not subject to the terms of this privacy policy?**

Contents shared by the user on site through reviews, online chat, blogs, messenger, forums, and discussion rooms, testimonials etc. are not considered as personal information and are not subject to the terms of this privacy policy.

  * **How does evok.in use customer information?**

We collect only information that is required to have a smooth transaction of user while buying online furniture through evok.in. We do not share our customer data/information with any other agency/third party.

We can share the customer information with our subsidiaries, business partners and affiliates, who are involved in delivery of services to you while in your product purchase process. We can share some or all your information as governed in case of acquisition or mergers with other business entity.

We can use some of the customer information for certain customer surveys/marketing research/ activities to understand customer’s buying behavior, his statistical/demographical profile, his past purchase history to grow our business relationship with him.

We can use customer’s personal information to provide him information related to promotions/ schemes/ offers/ delivery/shipping/product installation/service status/ help us to provide personalized features/tailor our sites/application to customer’s interest/to get in touch with customer when necessary. We provide option to our customers to opt out of these services.

Cookies can be used to provide better/modified buying experience to our customer e.g identifying recent viewed items, items in wish list and cart features.

We use session log and traffic flow information to understand how customers are interacting with our site and to improve on required field/s. Through this we understand and analyze customer behavior, visit preference, buying patterns etc.

We use customer’s computer system’s IP address, traffic sources, user navigation across the site, browser and order information to measure overall site performance with regards to number of users visited, time spent by them on site, their engagement, their preferred product etc.

We can use user/customer information in case required in for legal processes/dispute, comply with any statuary or regulatory requirement, troubleshooting, detecting/protecting any error/ fraud / other criminal/ illegal activity, collect fees owed, enforce our terms and conditions, prevent abuse of our services, prevent violation of the right of third parties/business partners/other users/ public in general etc.

We provide all users to opt out of receiving communication from Evok.in or on behalf of our business partners after creating an account with us. To remove your contact information from evok.in, please write to us at [onlinesupport@evok.in](mailto:help@evok.in)

In case of any inquiry/clarification with regards to your account, please write to us at [onlinesupport@evok.in](mailto:onlinesupport@evok.in)

  * **What choices are available to you regarding collection, use and distribution of your information?**

You may change your interests at any time and may opt-in or opt-out of any marketing / promotional / newsletters mailings. Evok reserves the right to send you certain service related communication, considered to be a part of your evok account without offering you the facility to opt-out. You may update your information and change your account settings at any time.

Upon request, we will remove/block your personally identifiable information from our database, thereby cancelling your registration. However, your information may remain stored in archive on our servers even after the deletion or the termination of your account.

If we plan to use your personally identifiable information for any commercial purposes, we will notify you at the time we collect that information and allow you to opt-out of having your information used for those purposes.

  * **Who collects the information?**

We collect anonymous traffic information when you visit our website/application. We collect personal identifiable information about you as a part of a voluntary registration process/contest/ any combination thereof. Our advertisers may collect anonymous traffic information from their owned assigned cookies to your browser. Our website/application contains links to other websites /applications. We are not responsible for any privacy practices of such websites/applications which we do not own/manage/control.

  * **What security does evok.in take to protect customer’s information from loss, misuse or alteration?**

To protect against loss/misuse/alteration of information under evok’s control, we have appropriate physical/electronic/managerial processes e.g. our servers are accessible to only authorized personnel and that customer’s information is shared with respective personnel on need to know basis to complete transaction and to provide the services requested by the customer.

Although we Endeavour to protect customer’s personal identifiable information, transmission made by means of internet/telecom/other networks cannot be made absolutely secure. By using evok.in customer/user agrees that evok has no liability for disclosure of your information due to error in transmission/unauthorized acts of third parties.

By submitting data to us or our agents or using the site, you consent to our use of your data in the manner set out in this privacy policy. We have copyright over this privacy policy. Use by third parties, even by way of extract, for commercial purpose is not allowed. Infringement may be subject to legal action.

  * **Are children allowed to use evok.in?**

Use of evok.in is available only to persons who can form a legally binding contract under the Indian Contract Act, 1872. If you are a minor i.e. under the age of 18 years, you may use evok.in only with the involvement of a parent or guardian.

**Policy update:** Evok.in reserves the right to change/update this policy to include/exclude clauses anytime by placing a prominent notice on our website. Such changes will be effective immediately upon posting to the website. Evok.in does not bear any responsibility for updating users on the same.

**Contact us:** Please do not hesitate to contact us regarding any matter relating to this privacy policy at [<onlinesupport@evok.in>](mailto:onlinesupport@evok.in)
